The Sudanese armed forces are being funded by Egypt, Qatar, Turkey, Iran, Saudi Arabia, and Russia.
But Amanda, why would Russia be on both sides?
Because for some, the goal of Sudan and utilizing its resources are more tangible resources in the sense of minerals and things like this.
However, all of these Arab countries are also vying for power, dominance over trade routes.
And Sudan sits on the Red Sea.
So when we're talking about reasons for war, we're not just talking about like physical minerals and labor, etc.
We're also talking about the actual earth.
Okay, we're talking about water and how these pathways allow for not only capitalism, but also power and dominance.
Now, according to Horn, the International Institute for Strategic Studies, which is a nonprofit applied research and policy think tank based in Nairobi, Kenya.
While the full implications of Russia's growing presence in Sudan remain uncertain, it could shift regional power dynamics, potentially affecting China's economic interests.
So when we talk about the motherland as it exists, we have to remember that this is still the biggest continent on the earth that has the most resources on the earth.
It is still being seen as a seat of necessary wealth in order for these other places to be powerful.
Thus, it becomes even more imperative that African nations see the strength in themselves.
Thus, it becomes more imperative that they may be able to receive applied to Asia.